<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Projects on Open Source Accelerator</title><link>goupaz.com/events/</link><description>Recent content in Projects on Open Source Accelerator</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 15:15:26 +1000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="goupaz.com/events/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>02hero</title><link>goupaz.com/events/02hero/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 12:33:46 +1000</pubDate><guid>goupaz.com/events/02hero/</guid><description>1.5-2 hours webinar hosted by domain experts. Desire to share &amp;amp; learn but the lack of community is not an issue anymore.
Host session Chapter03: April-June 2020 Line: Open Source - English
No Topic Slides MoM Video Date Speaker Country Co-host Register 1 02 Open Source Slides Logs Session01 18 April 2020 Kamran Ahmed Dubai expertech Link Chapter02: September-November 2019 Line: N/A - Video: Azerbaijani - Slides: English</description></item><item><title>techbrains</title><link>goupaz.com/events/techbrains/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 15:15:26 +1000</pubDate><guid>goupaz.com/events/techbrains/</guid><description>Engineers love build stuff, solve problems! This event is exception! Most effective network building event. The moment silence is not gold.
Chapter01: 18 January, 2020 Line: Intro - Video: Azerbaijani - Slides: English
Motivation Onboard Open Source community spirit Good Leaders talk about it People need your expertise, motivation, love Agenda Egoless, collaborative, competent, decentralized, scalable, fun community culture Structured and indexed data flow within community NOT IN Agenda Politics Religion Immigration Timeline All participants have 5mins and 1 slide to talk.</description></item><item><title>kiss.conf</title><link>goupaz.com/events/kissconf/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 15:14:54 +1000</pubDate><guid>goupaz.com/events/kissconf/</guid><description>kiss.conf - keep it stupid simple. Lightweight conference format can be organized in a week. Open to anyone, who has something to share with techies!
Host conference Chapter01: 09-10 May, 2020 Line: Open Source - English
Meeting of Minutes: - Day01 - Day02
Hosted by DAY 01 No Topic PPT Video Date Mentor -1 Promo Video N/A Session-1 08 MAY 2020 Sako M 0 Opening Ceremony slides Session0 09 MAY 2020, 18:45 Sako M 1 covid19 tech impact slides Session01 09 MAY 2020, 19:00 Vurgun HajiyevGarib M 2 Getting started with Meshery slides Session02 09 MAY 2020, 19:35 Lee Calcote 3 Open Source driven Career slides Session03 09 MAY 2020,20:10 Elshad Agayev 4 Building Open Source Developer Tool slides Session04 09 MAY 2020, 20:45 Tauqeer Nasir 5 NGINX Ingress Controller for Kubernetes slides Session05 09 MAY 2020, 21:20 Elvin Efendi DAY 02 No Topic PPT Video Date Mentor 1 OS Development slides Session06 10 MAY 2020, 19:00 Emin Guliyev 2 Modern Web Application Security slides Session07 10 MAY 202, 19:35 Mehemmed Rustamzadeh 3 LMS Microservices in production slides Session08 10 MAY 2020, 20:45 Imran Yusubov 4 DevOps in Action slides Session09 10 MAY 2020, 20:10 Sako M 5 Build your open source ERP slides Session10 10 MAY 2020, 21:20 Jumshud SultanovNurlan Farajov 0 Closing Ceremony N/A N/A 10 MAY 2020, 22:00 Nabi N</description></item></channel></rss>