<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Home on Open Source Accelerator</title><link>goupaz.com/</link><description>Recent content in Home on Open Source Accelerator</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 20 Dec 2018 13:45:06 +1000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="goupaz.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Vusal Ibrahimli</title><link>goupaz.com/team/vusalibrahimli/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2018 10:47:58 +1000</pubDate><guid>goupaz.com/team/vusalibrahimli/</guid><description>More than 10 years of experience and background in financial and data analysis, accounting.</description></item><item><title>02hero</title><link>goupaz.com/events/02hero/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 12:33:46 +1000</pubDate><guid>goupaz.com/events/02hero/</guid><description>1.5-2 hours webinar hosted by domain experts. Desire to share &amp;amp; learn but the lack of community is not an issue anymore.
Host session Chapter03: April-June 2020 Line: Open Source - English
No Topic Slides MoM Video Date Speaker Country Co-host Register 1 02 Open Source Slides Logs Session01 18 April 2020 Kamran Ahmed Dubai expertech Link Chapter02: September-November 2019 Line: N/A - Video: Azerbaijani - Slides: English</description></item><item><title>techbrains</title><link>goupaz.com/events/techbrains/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 15:15:26 +1000</pubDate><guid>goupaz.com/events/techbrains/</guid><description>Engineers love build stuff, solve problems! This event is exception! Most effective network building event. The moment silence is not gold.
Chapter01: 18 January, 2020 Line: Intro - Video: Azerbaijani - Slides: English
Motivation Onboard Open Source community spirit Good Leaders talk about it People need your expertise, motivation, love Agenda Egoless, collaborative, competent, decentralized, scalable, fun community culture Structured and indexed data flow within community NOT IN Agenda Politics Religion Immigration Timeline All participants have 5mins and 1 slide to talk.</description></item><item><title>Sako M</title><link>goupaz.com/team/sakom/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2018 10:47:58 +1000</pubDate><guid>goupaz.com/team/sakom/</guid><description>Sako’s international experience for the last 10 years he has worked for 7 tech companies in 6 different countries.</description></item><item><title>Robert Johnson</title><link>goupaz.com/team/staff-2/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Dec 2018 13:44:23 +1000</pubDate><guid>goupaz.com/team/staff-2/</guid><description>UI</description></item><item><title>kiss.conf</title><link>goupaz.com/events/kissconf/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 15:14:54 +1000</pubDate><guid>goupaz.com/events/kissconf/</guid><description>kiss.conf - keep it stupid simple. Lightweight conference format can be organized in a week. Open to anyone, who has something to share with techies!
Host conference Chapter01: 09-10 May, 2020 Line: Open Source - English
Meeting of Minutes: - Day01 - Day02
Hosted by DAY 01 No Topic PPT Video Date Mentor -1 Promo Video N/A Session-1 08 MAY 2020 Sako M 0 Opening Ceremony slides Session0 09 MAY 2020, 18:45 Sako M 1 covid19 tech impact slides Session01 09 MAY 2020, 19:00 Vurgun HajiyevGarib M 2 Getting started with Meshery slides Session02 09 MAY 2020, 19:35 Lee Calcote 3 Open Source driven Career slides Session03 09 MAY 2020,20:10 Elshad Agayev 4 Building Open Source Developer Tool slides Session04 09 MAY 2020, 20:45 Tauqeer Nasir 5 NGINX Ingress Controller for Kubernetes slides Session05 09 MAY 2020, 21:20 Elvin Efendi DAY 02 No Topic PPT Video Date Mentor 1 OS Development slides Session06 10 MAY 2020, 19:00 Emin Guliyev 2 Modern Web Application Security slides Session07 10 MAY 202, 19:35 Mehemmed Rustamzadeh 3 LMS Microservices in production slides Session08 10 MAY 2020, 20:45 Imran Yusubov 4 DevOps in Action slides Session09 10 MAY 2020, 20:10 Sako M 5 Build your open source ERP slides Session10 10 MAY 2020, 21:20 Jumshud SultanovNurlan Farajov 0 Closing Ceremony N/A N/A 10 MAY 2020, 22:00 Nabi N</description></item><item><title>devops</title><link>goupaz.com/projects/devops/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 15:14:39 +1000</pubDate><guid>goupaz.com/projects/devops/</guid><description/></item><item><title>python</title><link>goupaz.com/projects/python/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 15:14:39 +1000</pubDate><guid>goupaz.com/projects/python/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Lala Ells</title><link>goupaz.com/team/staff-1/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Dec 2018 13:44:55 +1000</pubDate><guid>goupaz.com/team/staff-1/</guid><description/></item><item><title>linux</title><link>goupaz.com/projects/os/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 15:15:34 +1000</pubDate><guid>goupaz.com/projects/os/</guid><description/></item><item><title>algo</title><link>goupaz.com/projects/algo/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 12:33:46 +1000</pubDate><guid>goupaz.com/projects/algo/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Susan Shelton</title><link>goupaz.com/team/staff-3/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Dec 2018 13:45:06 +1000</pubDate><guid>goupaz.com/team/staff-3/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Chapter01</title><link>goupaz.com/techbrains/chapter01/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 12:33:46 +1000</pubDate><guid>goupaz.com/techbrains/chapter01/</guid><description>Chapter01: June-August 2019 Line: Intro - Video: Azerbaijani - Slides: English
No Name Position Company Education Attendance Country 1 Garib M Founder WeTravel N/A Remote EU 2 Ramin Orujov Founder ITCITY N/A Remote AZE 3 Rovshan Musayev DevOps NN Group N/A Remote EU 4 Kanan Mammadli Lead Software Engineer EPAM N/A Remote USA 5 Emin Aliyev CEO Easymove Baku State University - Applied Mathematics and Economic Cybernetics Remote USA 6 Adil Adilli Software Engineer Microsoft University of Melbourne, MS, Mechatronics Engineering Remote USA 7 Said Samadli Software Engineer Techtronic Industries Greenville University of Tennessee Electrical Engineering &amp;amp; Computer Science Remote USA 8 Sabina Shahbazzadeh Software Engineer Techtronic Industries Greenville University of Tennessee Electrical Engineering &amp;amp; Computer Science Remote USA 9 Taleh Bayramov Software Developer in Test Ally Bank (Charlotte,NC) Azerbaijan State Economic University - Information Technology Remote USA 10 Sako M DevOps OpenGov MSc: ITU(US), Eurecom(France), Qafqaz Uni(Azerbaijan) Onsite USA 11 Jahangir Najafov Product Tech Manager Google Duke University - Fuqua School of Business Baku State University Onsite USA 12 Ibrahim Hasanov Founder Uviba Qafqaz University (Dropout) Minerva Schools at K.</description></item><item><title>Host Session</title><link>goupaz.com/02hero/howto/hostsession/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 12:33:46 +1000</pubDate><guid>goupaz.com/02hero/howto/hostsession/</guid><description>How to host a session/webinar Pre session
Find a speaker who are top in their field Direct message a speaker in linkedin/twitter/email (Optional) Arrange Zoom call to go through details, concerns, outcomes, success criterias, risks if any to include in CodeOfConduct Create slides from template and add speaker as a contributor in GoolgeSlide Create a register form in GoogleForm including: FullName, Email, Linkedin, Github(optional), Country, Any Comments fields Create a feedback form in GoogleForm including: what liked, disliked and how we can do better Create MeetingMinutes doc from template in GoogleDoc Create marketing post, after confirmed with speaker, included: Topic Brief description: who should join and what they will get Session Date, start/end hours Speaker, Role, Company Host, Role, Company Share in Linkedin, Twitter, Slack the post, include some statement which attractive, exciting, fun.</description></item><item><title>Use Cases</title><link>goupaz.com/techbrains/usecases/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 12:33:46 +1000</pubDate><guid>goupaz.com/techbrains/usecases/</guid><description>UC01 - Delicious food &amp;amp; Successful career Requirements Knowledge &amp;amp; experience = ingredients The money spend on ingredients = health variables(late sleep, long work hours etc.), time and cost(spend on trainings, commute etc.) Conclusion Right receipt makes food delicious! Which ingredient in which quality = X technology in junior level Which ingredient what time = X coding language, after Y one Which ingredient how much = 2 years in X company UC02 - Tribal Leadership There are 5 stages of community mindset:</description></item><item><title>About</title><link>goupaz.com/about/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2018 17:01:34 +0700</pubDate><guid>goupaz.com/about/</guid><description>Who we are? The GOUP project is the idea of Azerbaijani tech community living abroad.
Mission Build bridges between tech professionals in a collaborative ways across the borders.
Vision Make the world better place to live, using technology and right culture.
Objectives Build egoless, collaborative, competent, decentralized, scalable, fun community culture. Our goal is simple to structure and index the data flow within communities.</description></item><item><title>Join</title><link>goupaz.com/join/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2018 17:01:34 +0700</pubDate><guid>goupaz.com/join/</guid><description>Hey, join us, it&amp;rsquo;s fun :)
Slack
Github
Youtube
Facebook
Linkedin
Twitter</description></item><item><title/><link>goupaz.com/02hero/chapter01/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>goupaz.com/02hero/chapter01/</guid><description> Chapter01: June-August 2019 Line: N/A - Video: Azerbaijani - /events/02hero/slides: English
No Topic PPT Video Date Mentor Country 1 Global career in tech slides Session01 01 June Sako M USA 2 Cloud Technologies slides Session02 15 June Rovshan Musayev Czech 3 Database Technologies slides Session03 22 June Ramil Rahimov Canada 4 Network Technologies slides Session04 1 &amp;amp; 2 29 June Farid Akhundov Australia 5 DevOps slides Session05 06 July Alakbar Mammadov Norway 6 Microservice Architecture slides Session06 13 July Emin Hasanov Germany 7 System Engineering/Software Architecture slides Session07 20 July Emin Quliyev Azerbaijan 8 Algorithms slides Session08 27 July Vusal Ahmadoglu The Netherlan 9 Design and Behavior preparation slides Session09 03 August Emin Guliyev Germany X IT Security slides SessionX 11 August Rashad Suleymanov Poland</description></item><item><title/><link>goupaz.com/02hero/chapter02/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>goupaz.com/02hero/chapter02/</guid><description> Chapter02: September-November 2019 Line: N/A - Video: Azerbaijani - /events/02hero/slides: English
No Topic PPT Video Date Mentor Country 1 Intro to programming N/A Session01 08 September Tural Ismayilzade Estonia 2 The role of education system in our failure N/A Session02 15 September Togrul Samad UAE 3 Maybe my own business? N/A Session03 22 September Jasur Hasanov Azerbaijan 4 From Lawyer to Engineer in Uber slides Session04 29 September Orkhan Gasimli USA 5 Happy Frontend slides Session 05 06 October Orkhan Jafarov Azerbaijan 6 Software Design Patterns slides Session 06 13 October Zeynal Zeynalov Germany 7 Stream Processing slides Session 07 20 October Elkhan Shahverdi Estonia 8 The Pragmatic Programmer slides Session 08 27 October Vugar Gasimov Estonia 9 IT Security NA Session 09 02 November Fikret Kerimli USA XX Artificial Intelligence slides Session XX 03 November Rustam Hashimov USA</description></item><item><title/><link>goupaz.com/kissconf/howto/hostconference/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>goupaz.com/kissconf/howto/hostconference/</guid><description>How to host a conference Pre conference
Find partners Find sponsors Find a speaker who are top in their field Direct message a speaker in linkedin/twitter/email (Optional) Arrange Zoom call to go through details, concerns, outcomes, success criterias, risks if any to include in CodeOfConduct Create slides from template and add speaker as a contributor in GoolgeSlide Create a register form in GoogleForm including: FullName, Email, Linkedin, Github(optional), Country, Any Comments fields Create a feedback form in GoogleForm including: what liked, disliked and how we can do better Create MeetingMinutes doc from template in GoogleDoc Create marketing post, after confirmed with speaker, included: Topic Brief description: who should join and what they will get Session Date, start/end hours Speaker, Role, Company Host, Role, Company Share in Linkedin, Twitter, Slack the post, include some statement which attractive, exciting, fun.</description></item></channel></rss>