<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Hugo on GOUP</title><link>https://courses.goupaz.com/static-site-generators/hugo/</link><description>Recent content in Hugo on GOUP</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2017 20:24:10 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://courses.goupaz.com/static-site-generators/hugo/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Windows Installation</title><link>https://courses.goupaz.com/static-site-generators/hugo/installing-hugo-on-windows/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2017 20:24:10 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://courses.goupaz.com/static-site-generators/hugo/installing-hugo-on-windows/</guid><description>Often times, trying to install and setup programs can be a mess, either the instructions are unclear, or there’s too many little things to do that people end up messing up the first time around. Luckily, that’s not the case with Hugo. Windows Installation is really easy, and GOUP is here to guide you through every step.
Step 1 : Preparing Your Windows File System The first step when installing Hugo on windows is to make a space for it on your hard drive.</description></item><item><title>Mac Installation</title><link>https://courses.goupaz.com/static-site-generators/hugo/installing-hugo-on-mac/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2017 20:24:11 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://courses.goupaz.com/static-site-generators/hugo/installing-hugo-on-mac/</guid><description>Often times, trying to install and setup programs can be a mess, either the instructions aren&amp;rsquo;t clear, or there’s too many little things to do that people end up messing up the first time around. Luckily, that’s not the case with Hugo. Mac Installation is really easy, and GOUP is here to guide you through every step.
Step 1 : Installing Homebrew Installing programs on mac isn’t the same as installing them on Windows.</description></item><item><title>Creating A New Site</title><link>https://courses.goupaz.com/static-site-generators/hugo/hugo-directory-structure/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2017 20:24:11 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://courses.goupaz.com/static-site-generators/hugo/hugo-directory-structure/</guid><description>Creating a new website in Hugo is simple and fast. With a couple commands you’ll be up and running and ready to start adding content.
Preparing your workspace Once you have everything installed and ready to go it’s time to create a new Hugo website. The first thing you want to think about is folder structure. When you’re building a website It’s important to organize your content in a simple way.</description></item><item><title>Installing &amp; Using Themes</title><link>https://courses.goupaz.com/static-site-generators/hugo/installing-using-themes/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2017 20:24:11 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://courses.goupaz.com/static-site-generators/hugo/installing-using-themes/</guid><description>Themes are collections of hugo layouts that take all the hassle out of building your site. If you’re not inclined to learn how to write HTML and CSS, or if you simply want to get your blog or content site up as soon as possible then themes are for you. There are dozens of publicly available pre-built themes available for download that developers in the hugo community have built. Using a pre-built theme takes all the hassle out of designing and organizing your hugo site.</description></item><item><title>Content Organization</title><link>https://courses.goupaz.com/static-site-generators/hugo/content-organization/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2017 20:24:12 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://courses.goupaz.com/static-site-generators/hugo/content-organization/</guid><description>Content is the cornerstone of any good website or blog. Hugo makes it easy to organize and manage large amounts of content.
Types of content in hugo Scalability should be the cornerstone of any good website. As your website grows and evolves you want to make sure that it’s able to accommodate a large number of pages and a rich variety of content. Hugo is very aware of the need for good content management, and has content guidelines built it to help users make their websites super scalable.</description></item><item><title>Front Matter</title><link>https://courses.goupaz.com/static-site-generators/hugo/front-matter/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2017 20:24:12 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://courses.goupaz.com/static-site-generators/hugo/front-matter/</guid><description>Hugo makes it really easy to write static content for the web. But not only is hugo easy to use, it’s also super powerful. In this lesson we’re gonna look at one of the most powerful tools Hugo has in it’s arsenal, front matter.
Front matter When you create a new content page using the hugo new filename command, hugo automatically creates a new file and fills it with some default information.</description></item><item><title>Archetypes</title><link>https://courses.goupaz.com/static-site-generators/hugo/archetypes/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2017 20:24:12 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://courses.goupaz.com/static-site-generators/hugo/archetypes/</guid><description>When you create a new page using the hugo new command, Hugo automatically populates the page with several front matter attributes. By default you get the title, date and a draft attribute. But what if you want to add more attributes by default. For example if you wanted to store the author of a page in the front matter on all your pages. Hugo has a way where you can define what the default front matter will be on each page.</description></item><item><title>Shortcodes</title><link>https://courses.goupaz.com/static-site-generators/hugo/shortcodes/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2017 20:24:13 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://courses.goupaz.com/static-site-generators/hugo/shortcodes/</guid><description>Built-in Shortcodes Hugo has a collection of built-in shortcodes which you can use right out of the box. For a full listing of built in shortcodes check out the official hugo documentation page: https://gohugo.io/content-management/shortcodes/#using-shortcodes</description></item><item><title>Taxonomies</title><link>https://courses.goupaz.com/static-site-generators/hugo/taxonomies/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2017 20:24:13 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://courses.goupaz.com/static-site-generators/hugo/taxonomies/</guid><description>Taxonomies are hugo’s way of letting users group content together. Taxonomies allow users to classify their content, and represent relationships in a variety of ways.
To really wrap your head around what taxonomies are and what they do, it will be helpful to look at a real world example. A simple example of a taxonomy in real life is music genres. Throughout the ages music has been classified into various groups.</description></item><item><title>Template Basics</title><link>https://courses.goupaz.com/static-site-generators/hugo/introduction-to-templates/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2017 20:24:14 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://courses.goupaz.com/static-site-generators/hugo/introduction-to-templates/</guid><description/></item><item><title>List Page Templates</title><link>https://courses.goupaz.com/static-site-generators/hugo/list-page-templates/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2017 20:24:14 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://courses.goupaz.com/static-site-generators/hugo/list-page-templates/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Single Page Templates</title><link>https://courses.goupaz.com/static-site-generators/hugo/single-page-templates/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2017 20:24:15 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://courses.goupaz.com/static-site-generators/hugo/single-page-templates/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Home Page Templates</title><link>https://courses.goupaz.com/static-site-generators/hugo/home-page-templates/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2017 20:24:15 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://courses.goupaz.com/static-site-generators/hugo/home-page-templates/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Section Templates</title><link>https://courses.goupaz.com/static-site-generators/hugo/section-templates/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2017 20:24:15 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://courses.goupaz.com/static-site-generators/hugo/section-templates/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Block Templates</title><link>https://courses.goupaz.com/static-site-generators/hugo/block-templates/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2017 20:24:16 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://courses.goupaz.com/static-site-generators/hugo/block-templates/</guid><description>Block templates give developers a way to supercharge the amount of control they have over templates and layouts. By incorporating block templates into your hugo website design, you’ll seriously increase the scalability and modularity of your site.
Block temples are an advanced type of hugo template that allows you to build high level templates by specifying specific blocks of content which can be implemented by lower level templates. It’s a very powerful feature for building complex layouts and template structures.</description></item><item><title>Variables</title><link>https://courses.goupaz.com/static-site-generators/hugo/variables/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2017 20:24:16 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://courses.goupaz.com/static-site-generators/hugo/variables/</guid><description>Hugo is written in the Go programming language. The go language includes a small library called go HTML template. Go HTML template allows you to use logic inside your html templates to make more complex layouts and pages. It’s essentially like a mini programming language that can be used in HTML and markdown files. Hugo leverages go html templates to allow logic to be used inside templates.
Image of the go programming language logo with the hugo logo</description></item><item><title>Functions</title><link>https://courses.goupaz.com/static-site-generators/hugo/functions/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2017 20:24:16 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://courses.goupaz.com/static-site-generators/hugo/functions/</guid><description>Go template functions give you a series of useful functions that you can use to add logic into your templates. These functions perform a variety of tasks like adding numbers, splicing strings or looping through lists of values.
How functions work Functions are formatted as follows
Copy{{ func-name arg1, arg2, … , argX }} Inside double curly brackets, you put the name of the function and then pass the function arguments.</description></item><item><title>Conditionals</title><link>https://courses.goupaz.com/static-site-generators/hugo/conditionals/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2017 20:24:17 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://courses.goupaz.com/static-site-generators/hugo/conditionals/</guid><description>Conditionals are a common tool used in programming to help the computer make decisions. In our case we can use conditionals to tell hugo when we want it to do certain things. Conditionals are realized in the form of if statements. If statements are pieces of code that we use to tell hugo what we want it to do in certain situations.
A good example of a conditional is when you go to an amusement park.</description></item><item><title>Data Templates</title><link>https://courses.goupaz.com/static-site-generators/hugo/data-templates/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2017 20:24:17 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://courses.goupaz.com/static-site-generators/hugo/data-templates/</guid><description>Data is the backbone of any good website. Often times, even with a static site, there will be certain information that you want to store separate from your actual content files. Hugo makes it really easy to store static data in custom TOML, YAML or JSON files. This data acts as a type of database that hugo partials and layouts can pull information from.
All Hugo data is stored in the Data folder at the root of the site.</description></item><item><title>Partial Templates</title><link>https://courses.goupaz.com/static-site-generators/hugo/partial-templates/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2017 20:24:18 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://courses.goupaz.com/static-site-generators/hugo/partial-templates/</guid><description>One of the most important factors in building any website is scalability. If your website can’t scale to accommodate hundreds or thousands of pages then it will eventually fail. Modularity is the answer to building a site that scales well and hugo’s answer to modularity is partial templates.
Modularity Modularity is a concept which relates to breaking your website into a series of parts.
For example on a normal website you have three main sections:</description></item><item><title>Shortcode Templates</title><link>https://courses.goupaz.com/static-site-generators/hugo/shortcode-templates/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2017 20:24:18 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://courses.goupaz.com/static-site-generators/hugo/shortcode-templates/</guid><description>Often times when you’re writing content for your blog or website, there will be certain components that you are using multiple times across all your posts. Maybe you like to surround all your images with a stylish CSS border, or you embed youtube videos into your posts. These components all use the same code and logic. Instead of having to copy and paste this code whenever we want to include one of these component, it would be easier to just put the code in one central place and have hugo insert it into our pages when it builds our site.</description></item><item><title>Building &amp; Hosting</title><link>https://courses.goupaz.com/static-site-generators/hugo/building-hosting/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2017 20:24:18 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://courses.goupaz.com/static-site-generators/hugo/building-hosting/</guid><description>Up until this point you’ve most likely been running and testing your hugo website using the hugo server command. Hugo server is a great way to test and track changes locally, but what about when you’re ready to display your creation to the world.
When you&amp;rsquo;re creating all of your layouts, partials and content pages your website is scattered into a bunch of pieces. But when you build your website all of those pieces get put together is exactly the way you want by hugo.</description></item></channel></rss>